It looks to be a wet one tomorrow with scattered showers throughout the day.
Suppose I won't be hanging anything outside to dry tomorrow.
Grandma, I'm home!
Oh, hi. Want a snack?
There's something I gotta check first.
Sure, no hurry.
Oh, come on! Why are you so slow?
I'm not used to Ayumu's laptop.
Here we go.
Oh, I'm not used to...
Whoa, holy crap!
Yoda really is trying to gather all the Selectors together.
It's happening really close to here, too.
Oh, sorry.
Thank you.
Yeah.
Ruko?
This is...
They're only one building away from a Tetris, and then the whole city might just disappear
on us.
Ruko?
Is something wrong?
Uh-uh.
Not at all.
Ruko, listen.
If something's bothering you, or if you've got something on your mind, say it.
Uh...
Yuzuki...
Is it... true?
Am I scary?
Cause people say they never know what I'm thinking.
Huh?
No, that wasn't what I was trying to say before.
I meant you try to figure things out all on your own and hold everything inside.
Uh...
You know, kinda like I do.
I'm sorry, okay?
Still friends, right?
Like back when we bought these?
Of course we are.
You're one of the kindest people I've ever known.
What?
Hey, come on, knock it off.
You're making me blush.
Turns out you're also one of the strongest.
Oh...
I wish...
I could be like that.
Yuzuki...
Toma...
I'm sorry.
I've decided to battle Iyona.
What are you talking about?
I thought you said you gave up battling.
Yeah, I did.
The thing is...
Now, I have a wish to fight for.
It's...
A good one.
It's to save you.
You and Toma.
Plus everyone else who became Elrigs.
I swear.
I'll bring you all back to normal.
I'll get you out of this crazy game.
I don't care what I have to sacrifice to do it.
That's my one and only wish.
Oh, bro.
That's sweet, but it can't be done.
I'm sorry.
Why not?
Because like me, every Elrig used to be a normal girl.
And the Elrigs who replace winning selectors become normal girls again.
Even though they're bound by an oath to fulfill your wish, there's a limit to what they can do.
So you're telling me there are some wishes that can never come true, like going back in time or reshaping reality?
That's correct.
But it's not my place to decide which are possible and which are not.
What?
Most wishes can come true thanks to the efforts of the Elrig, assuming of course that she upholds her end of the oath.
Whether it's due to personal morality, common sense, or simply a matter of self-preservation, an Elrig may become reluctant.
But she must cast these feelings aside and prioritize the selectors' wish above her own life.
If an Elrig refuses the wish, she will remain trapped in her card, unable to return to the outside world.
Therefore, to guarantee both the wish and her eventual escape from her card, from the moment they meet, she must do anything and everything to reach that conclusion.
Even deceiving her selector.
That's what...
Otherwise, you wouldn't agree to the ritual of acknowledgement.
It's a catalyst, you see. A trigger for the transformation.
Now, the oath. Do you remember it?
Yeah. It's, uh... I accept...
The laws of the Selector.
I accept the laws of the Selector.
And, um...
And upon this sacred oath, the new Eternal Girl shall be born!
Once an Eternal Girl, she is obligated to fulfill the wish that has been made.
Though she may have deceived you, she has entered a contract that cannot be broken.
For if she fails to uphold her end, the Eternal Girl will disappear.
Remember what Hanayo said?
About how you couldn't wish Hitoi's memories back.
That probably means you can't just undo things with another wish.
Yeah, but those girls, the ones who are Elric's...
I have no idea how to get them out or if it's even possible, but...
This Mayu girl? The one in that weird white room? She might.
I just don't know how to get back to that place to ask her.
Maybe I can get them out.
Huh?
I'm not sure why, but somewhere deep down, they feel like I might know how.
I think I might be able to turn all the Elrics back to normal.
Uh...
You really think so?
Yeah, kinda.
But there's this feeling, something inside saying,
Yes, I can do this thing.
Well, maybe...
Tama...
Makes me wonder.
Uh...
No, that's crazy.
If the Eternal Girls have so little power,
what's the point in going through all this mess in the first place?
We're stuck in a card and they die if they can't fulfill the wish?
If we couldn't make the wish come true and they're us now,
then aren't you condemning us all?
There are exceptions.
That is to say, some Eternal Girls are more special than others.
You may lack the power to create this fairytale ending you so desire,
but there is magic yet in this world.
You expect me to buy into some fantasy mumbo-jumbo like that?
Given what you have just been through,
I'm surprised you would deny the very concept so flippantly.
And now it seems the time has come.
Morning dawns on your life as an Elric.
You now go to meet your selector.
No, wait! Tell me who you are!
I'm the one who will always be here,
in the rift that exists between the world of the cards and the world of reality.
Good luck, and goodbye.
You know, Tama does seem awfully different from other Elrics.
Maybe she's one of those so-called special ones.
So, maybe my wish can come true.
No dice.
What?
Remember, if you take the oath,
you're just going to turn into an Elric like I did.
Right.
But still,
since my wish is to release all the Elrics from their cards and make them real again,
maybe that means I won't be able to become one.
Are you nuts?
For all you know,
we could get fixed while you're stuck as an Elric forever!
Or, God forbid, something worse!
I know, but I…
Ruko, please! You've got to give this more thought!
I mean, sure, if you're a card, maybe I could find you.
And maybe we could be friends like we are now.
But…
People who aren't selectors,
like your grandmother and brother,
they'll never see you again!
Uh…
...
Hitoe?
Sorry, but I'd like my Elric back now.
Uh…
Hitoi, look, I, uh...
I don't care. Just give her back, okay?
Hitoi!
Hold on! We need to talk!
Yeah! Calm down! It's cool!
I just...
I don't want to hear it, and I have nothing to say to you.
Hitoi!
No way!
Hitoi?
I'm taking my L-Rig, and I'm going to compete in Eona's fan event.
If you want to talk to me so badly, you can do it on the battlefield.
If my wish comes true, I might never see Grandma again.
What should I do?
Grandma!
Oh, hello.
Yes, she's fine.
She's even made friends.
Hmm, she sure did.
What's that?
There's no point blaming yourself for this, not anymore.
I'm tired of hearing it. This has all been settled before.
And I won't have you pretending to be her mother, either.
I don't hold a thing against you, but when you said you weren't meant to be a parent, I was inclined to agree, and my opinion hasn't changed.
Remember, I love having the kids here.
Ayumu and Ruko are both utter joys.
They always brighten my day.
Uh, yes. Right. Okay, I'll call you then. You take care now.
Hi, Rue. You about ready for dinner?
Was that Mom?
Guess what? I finally thought of a wish.
Oh, is that so?
Uh-huh.
You see, when I was little, Mom and Dad were supposed to be close, but all they did was fight.
It made me sad.
It made me think if you got close to someone, you'd just end up getting hurt.
So I stayed away from people.
Well, except for you and Ayumu, of course.
I didn't think I needed anyone else but you guys.
But over the last few weeks, that's changed.
I've actually made some true friends, and they're real important to me, too.
And it's because of them that, well...
You were telling me the other day you hoped you could do something for your friends.
Is this wish of yours for them?
It's not something bad.
No, of course not. I mean...
So it's something good, then.
Well, yeah. I think it is.
It kind of has to be.
You have a good heart, Rue.
And you believe your wish is good.
The very fact that you wished it for your friends instead of for yourself proves to me you're probably on the right track.
So you do what you need to, dear.
And I'm sure it will come true.
Your friends are very lucky to have you, and so am I.
Grandma!
Oh, it's all right.
There's no reason to cry.
Who?
Rue?
Huh?
So you're gonna battle?
Mm-hmm.
We're gonna take on that mean girl, Leona, again.
I bet you can't wait.
No, I don't want to!
Huh?
Your grandma doesn't know what could happen.
If she did, she wouldn't have said all that.
She wouldn't let you risk your life.
I don't care if I'm stuck in this dump cart forever.
It's better than being alone.
You may never see me or your grandma again.
So please don't do this, Rue.
I don't want to lose you.
But Tama, I'm sure my plan is gonna work.
But Yuzuki said it might not.
Then what'll happen?
I'm sorry, but I've gotta do this.
I won't become an L-Rig and I won't let you stay one.
I promise.
We'll never be apart.
Really, you and I will do everything together.
Have yummy breakfasts with grandma.
Runs or not late to school.
Hang out with Yuzuki and Hitoi.
We'll all be best friends.
It's closed now, but during the summer.
We'll go to the candy shop on the corner.
They've got this ice cream you wouldn't believe.
We'll try a new flavor every day.
Trust me, you'll love it.
So, sound good?
It does.
But no.
Don't do it.
I'm sorry, Tama.
I am.
But I have to finish this.
Be careful now.
Okay, Rue?
Okay.
Think you'll be home in time for dinner?
Good question.
I'll try.
And do you think we could have potatoes au gratin?
With lots of bacon the way you like?
Oh, please.
Love you, Grandma.
All right.
Here goes.
Oh, wow.
These girls.
All of them are selectors here to fight for their wishes.
Ladies, welcome to the fan event.
Rather, welcome to the selectors-only WeCross party.
This building is owned by my father, and the work crews are off today.
So we don't have to worry about being disturbed.
We've all been battling to make our wishes come true.
And yet, we don't know how many wins we need to make that happen.
Frustrating, isn't it?
I started to wonder.
What if there was something we could do to change that?
Hence this party.
With so many selectors gathered to do battle.
Some are bound to win enough to meet these elusive conditions.
As a result, a large number of eternal girls will be born right here today.
These selectors.
They have no clue.
Now, obviously, for each of you who wins, there will be another who loses.
Speaking personally, I have no desire to fight anyone but the strongest selectors available.
Therefore, I have assigned you all to tournament brackets.
If you win a battle, you progress to the next round.
If you lose, you're out.
This will at least prevent multiple losses.
And the selector who makes it all the way to the top?
Well, you'll be facing me, of course.
Twelfth floor, room four?
Is everyone ready?
I hope so.
Because the battle begins now.
Open!
Tama Grove, gothic foundry.
I know it hurts.
But when I'm finished, none of you will ever have to go through this again.
Summon Mitsuruki.
This is the final blow, Tama.
Tama?
Tama!
Please, I need you to agree to this.
Otherwise, my wish won't come true.
I'm sorry, Tama.
But we have to do it my way.
We have to keep battling.
I should have seen this coming.
Guess so.
You ready to talk to me now?
Like I said, on the battlefield.
Open!
No new eternal girls have been born yet.
Not that I sense.
Oh, well.
On the other hand,
it looks like some selectors are losing their third and final battles.
I will find my way there.
To that white room.
Where she's waiting.
Mount Sevieryia and attack!
Yuzuki!
Grow now!
And banish Mikigami!
Dang it.
She's so much better than before.
Splitting conviction.
Tama!
Sorry!
Yuzuki, attack!
Banish Square!
Hit away.
It's wrong.
It's all wrong.
What do you mean, wrong?
It's not supposed to be like this.
Why can't you remember how it was when we played before?
Ruko.
We used to play for fun.
Not to win.
No Elrigs.
No battles.
No wishes.
Back then,
I thought that wasn't enough.
I wanted serious battles.
Serious victories.
Instead of just appreciating what I had.
Me too.
Now it's gone.
We can never just enjoy playing games again as friends.
And I hate it.
I knew it.
Now she's sad too.
That means she must remember.
She still has memories of us.
You think?
Hitoi, listen.
Like Ruko said, we all used to be friends.
What?
No, stop!
Did that hurt?
I'm sorry.
But I need you to remember.
Knock it off, Yuzuki!
You're hurting her!
I know, but do you want her to stay like this?
Her life being controlled by these stupid battles?
I don't.
I want to be best friends like we were!
Me too!
I don't want to battle like this!
I want to do it as friends like we used to!
It was so much fun!
Please remember!
No, please stop it!
This is killing me!
Hitoi, remember!
Your wish to make friends already came true!
You can quit all of this!
You still have us!
Stop it!
You can do this, Hitoi!
Just remember how it used to be!
Would you please just shut up?
I don't want to hear any more of this!
I just want to make my wish come true, that's all!
Aren't you listening?
I told you, it already did!
So...
Stop it!
No, okay!
This wasn't part of the deal!
You promised we would battle and you'd grant me a wish!
I...
Where's Crunchy?
She still has it!
Now then...
Ready to say goodbye!
I've waited long enough already!
Soon I will face my final battle as Yona Uruzoe!
Oh, one final note!
What's been a blast giving beatdowns to other Selectors with you!
I'm not gonna miss you one bit, you rotten bitch!
Still, I'll be beside you to the very end!
Selector!
Next time, that choice!
Next time, that choice.